<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Troop-Required on Boy Scouts Troop 201</title><link>https://aztroop201.org/tags/troop-required/</link><description>Recent content in Troop-Required on Boy Scouts Troop 201</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Troop 201 -</copyright><atom:link href="https://aztroop201.org/tags/troop-required/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Committee Chair</title><link>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/committee-chair/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/committee-chair/</guid><description>Position Description The troop committee chair is appointed by the chartered organization and/or the troop committee to see that all required committee functions are carried out. The troop committee chair appoints and supervises the unit committee and leaders, and organizes all committee to see that all troop responsibilities are delegated, coordinated and completed.
Duties Organize the committee to see that all functions are delegated, coordinated, and completed. Ensure that all training is in place and work with the Training Coordinator to validate the charter training needs are recorded.</description></item><item><title>Scoutmaster</title><link>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/scoutmaster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/scoutmaster/</guid><description>Position Description The Scoutmaster is responsible for training and guiding youth leaders in the operation of the troop, and for managing, training, and supporting his or her assistant Scoutmasters in their role.
Duties Conduct the Boy Scout program according to the policies of the Boy Scouts of America. Train youth leaders by conducting, at least yearly, an introduction to leadership and a team-building workshop. Conduct an annual troop program planning conference to assist youth leaders in planning the troop program.</description></item><item><title>Charter Representative</title><link>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/charter-representative/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/charter-representative/</guid><description>Description The Chartered Organization Representative is the direct contact between the unit and the Chartered Organization. This individual is also the organization&amp;rsquo;s contact with the district committee and the Local Council. The chartered organization representative may become a member of the district committee and is a voting member of the council. The Chartered Organization Representative appoints the unit committee chair.
Duties Serve as a member of the unit Key 3 team and meet together several times a year.</description></item><item><title>Unit Commissioner</title><link>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/unit-commissioner/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/unit-commissioner/</guid><description>Description The commissioner’s specific mission is to keep units operating at maximum efficiency so that they can deliver a good program to a growing youth membership.
Today’s commissioners are results-oriented rather than procedures-oriented. They are successful in their mission when units continue to operate, units regularly accept new youth, and units effectively deliver the ideals of Scouting to their members.
Commissioners are involved with carrying programs to the unit, and their main concern is to develop strength within the unit operation.</description></item><item><title>Assistant Scoutmaster</title><link>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/assistant-scoutmaster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/assistant-scoutmaster/</guid><description>Position Description An assistant Scoutmaster is an adult leader over the age of 18 who helps the Scoutmaster deliver the promise of Scouting. Each assistant Scoutmaster is assigned specific program duties. They can serve the troop by guiding a particular patrol to which they’ve been assigned, advising certain Scouts who’ve assumed a position e.g. the quartermaster or OA representative, or fill in as necessary to assure the junior leaders have what they need to run things.</description></item><item><title>Advancement Coordinator</title><link>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/advancement-coordinator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/advancement-coordinator/</guid><description>Duties Encourage Scouts to advance in rank. Work with the troop scribe to maintain all Scout advancement records. Arrange quarterly troop boards of review and courts of honor. Develop and maintain a merit badge counselor list. Make a prompt report on the correct form to the council service center when a troop board of review is held. Secure badges and certificates. Work with the troop librarian to build and maintain a troop library of merit badge pamphlets and other advancement literature.</description></item><item><title>Secretary</title><link>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/secretary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/secretary/</guid><description>Duties Keep minutes of meetings and send out committee meeting notices. Ensure that Scoutbook Calendar is up to date and all events are registered. Maintain member health forms and perform annual audit. Handle all Troop communications. Handle publicity. Prepare a family newsletter or web page of troop events and activities. Conduct the troop resource survey. At each meeting, report the minutes of the previous meeting. Position History Diana Kaminski 2021-2024 Anthony Wehry 2019-2021 Sean Bridges 2015-2019 Cynthia Welt 2011-2015</description></item><item><title>Treasurer</title><link>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/treasurer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/treasurer/</guid><description>Duties Handle all troop funds. Pay bills on recommendation of the Scoutmaster and authorization of the troop committee. Maintain checking and savings accounts. Keep adequate records in the Troop/ream Record Book. Supervise money-earning projects, including obtaining proper authorizations. Supervise the camp savings plan. Lead in the preparation of the annual troop budget. Lead the Friends of Scouting campaign. Report to the troop committee at each meeting. Manage grocery fundraising programs Bashas Fry&amp;rsquo;s Position History Ted Harrison 2012-2016</description></item></channel></rss>