<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Troop on Boy Scouts Troop 201</title><link>https://aztroop201.org/tags/troop/</link><description>Recent content in Troop on Boy Scouts Troop 201</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Troop 201 -</copyright><atom:link href="https://aztroop201.org/tags/troop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Scoutmaster</title><link>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/scoutmaster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/scoutmaster/</guid><description>Position Description The Scoutmaster is responsible for training and guiding youth leaders in the operation of the troop, and for managing, training, and supporting his or her assistant Scoutmasters in their role.
Duties Conduct the Boy Scout program according to the policies of the Boy Scouts of America. Train youth leaders by conducting, at least yearly, an introduction to leadership and a team-building workshop. Conduct an annual troop program planning conference to assist youth leaders in planning the troop program.</description></item><item><title>Assistant Scoutmaster</title><link>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/assistant-scoutmaster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/assistant-scoutmaster/</guid><description>Position Description An assistant Scoutmaster is an adult leader over the age of 18 who helps the Scoutmaster deliver the promise of Scouting. Each assistant Scoutmaster is assigned specific program duties. They can serve the troop by guiding a particular patrol to which they’ve been assigned, advising certain Scouts who’ve assumed a position e.g. the quartermaster or OA representative, or fill in as necessary to assure the junior leaders have what they need to run things.</description></item><item><title>Eagle Advisor</title><link>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/eagle-advisor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/eagle-advisor/</guid><description>Position Description</description></item></channel></rss>