<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Key-Three on Boy Scouts Troop 201</title><link>https://aztroop201.org/tags/key-three/</link><description>Recent content in Key-Three on Boy Scouts Troop 201</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Troop 201 -</copyright><atom:link href="https://aztroop201.org/tags/key-three/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Committee Chair</title><link>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/committee-chair/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/committee-chair/</guid><description>Position Description The troop committee chair is appointed by the chartered organization and/or the troop committee to see that all required committee functions are carried out. The troop committee chair appoints and supervises the unit committee and leaders, and organizes all committee to see that all troop responsibilities are delegated, coordinated and completed.
Duties Organize the committee to see that all functions are delegated, coordinated, and completed. Ensure that all training is in place and work with the Training Coordinator to validate the charter training needs are recorded.</description></item><item><title>Scoutmaster</title><link>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/scoutmaster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/scoutmaster/</guid><description>Position Description The Scoutmaster is responsible for training and guiding youth leaders in the operation of the troop, and for managing, training, and supporting his or her assistant Scoutmasters in their role.
Duties Conduct the Boy Scout program according to the policies of the Boy Scouts of America. Train youth leaders by conducting, at least yearly, an introduction to leadership and a team-building workshop. Conduct an annual troop program planning conference to assist youth leaders in planning the troop program.</description></item><item><title>Charter Representative</title><link>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/charter-representative/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/charter-representative/</guid><description>Description The Chartered Organization Representative is the direct contact between the unit and the Chartered Organization. This individual is also the organization&amp;rsquo;s contact with the district committee and the Local Council. The chartered organization representative may become a member of the district committee and is a voting member of the council. The Chartered Organization Representative appoints the unit committee chair.
Duties Serve as a member of the unit Key 3 team and meet together several times a year.</description></item></channel></rss>