<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Annual on Boy Scouts Troop 201</title><link>https://aztroop201.org/tags/annual/</link><description>Recent content in Annual on Boy Scouts Troop 201</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Troop 201 -</copyright><atom:link href="https://aztroop201.org/tags/annual/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Popcorn Fundraising</title><link>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/fundraising-popcorn/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/fundraising-popcorn/</guid><description>Position History Leslie O&amp;rsquo;Shea 2016-2021</description></item><item><title>Fiesta Bowl</title><link>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/fundraising-fiestabowl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/fundraising-fiestabowl/</guid><description>Description Run, lead and organize our yearly participation in the Fiesta Bowl parade cleanup for our troop fundraising.
Duties Manage relationship with Fiesta Bowl Committee. Communicate with troop expectations and timing of events. Ensure equipment is ordered for position with Fiesta Bowl staff. Attend pre and post parade meetings to ensure troop representation. Coordinate with the Pack for horse duty. Coordinate with fiesta bowl for game parties in addition to the parade.</description></item><item><title>Holiday Greens</title><link>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/fundraising-greens/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/fundraising-greens/</guid><description>Description Run and Lead our annual holiday greens fundraiser for the troop and pack.
Duties Manage relationship with vendor. Coordinate communications and determine budget for Troop vs Individual scout accounts. Determine pricing, materials and target fundraising goals. Coordinate the collection of orders for submission to the holiday greens vendors. Coordinate the collection of money and payment of all invoices. Coordinate the distribution of orders.</description></item><item><title>Scouting for Food Coordinator</title><link>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/service-scountingforfood/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aztroop201.org/volunteer/service-scountingforfood/</guid><description>Duties Coordinate with Vista Del Camino for pickup. Ensure that troop youth leaders have maps of collection area. Ensure that flyers are prepared and ready for handout Coordinate the pickup and delivery of collected food. Position History Keri Cavanaugh 2016-2021 Sean Bridges 2016-2020</description></item></channel></rss>